const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'Which of these is not a standard beer ingredient?',
      answers: [
        'Wheat',
        'Barley',
        'Hops',
        'Water',
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Wheat',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of these is not a variety of hop?',
      answers: [
        'Galaxy',
        'Citra',
        'Pale',
        'Mosaic',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Pale',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which style of beer is known for its bitter, hoppy flavor?',
      answers: [
        'Stout',
        'Lager',
        'Gose',
        'IPA',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'IPA',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which beer brand boasts the slogan "Find Your Beach"?',
      answers: [
        'Michelob',
        'Modelo',
        'Corona',
        'Dos Equis',
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Corona',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does the abbreviation IBU stand for?',
      answers: [
        'Independent Brewers Union',
        'International Bitterness Unit',
        'International Beverage Union',
        'Independent Beverage Unification',
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'International Bitterness Unit',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does ABV stand for?',
      answers: [
        'American Beverage Volition',
        'Annual Brewers Vacation',
        'Alcohol By Volume',
        'Alcoholic Beverage Vanguard',
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Alcohol By Volume',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which beer is known for its mascot who is a knight?',
      answers: [
      'Miller Lite',
      'Bud Light',
      'Coors Light',
      'Michelob Light',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Bud Light',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does PBR stand for?',
      answers: [
        'Personal Beverage Refrigerator',
        'Personal Beer Reserve',
        'Precious Beverage Rations',
        'Pabst Blue Ribbon',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Pabst Blue Ribbon',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which beer brand is represented by a spokesperson who has a reputation for being "the most interesting man in the world"?',
      answers: [
      'Michelob Ultra',
      'Heineken',
      'Dos Equis',
      'Modelo',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Dos Equis',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which beer claims to be "cold as the Rockies"?',
      answers: [
        'Natural Ice',
        'Miller Lite',
        'Keystone Light',
        'Coors Light',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Coors Light',
    }
];
